<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">University Times App</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="message">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_html">Display HTML</string>
    <string name="dummyHead">North Korea bombs new york with a nuclear missile strike</string>
    <string name="dummyBody">The first motion was an existing motion which is set to expire next 
        year in accordance with protocol, and was put before Congress to retain or see lapse. 
        The motion, titled ‘female participation  sought to mandate the USI Equality officer to 
        run a campaign highlighting the ‘persistent inequalities between men and women in Irish 
        society’ and to work with other organisations who ‘share (our) vision for an equal society’. 
        A number of student delegates spoke for and against the motion, with those in opposition 
        arguing that the motion was ‘offensive’ and ‘insulting’ to women.
        
        A second motion, proposed by Saint Angela’s College Students’ Union, sought to realise 
        greater female participation within the student movement, arguing that such a move would 
        lead to the perception of USI as a ‘more inclusive structure’. In a repeat of many of the 
        arguments made during the earlier debate, a number of delegates spoke of the ‘discriminatory’ 
        nature of the motion, with a general sentiment suggesting the impetus to seek public office 
        was the responsibility of the individual and USI should not actively seek to promote greater 
        female participation within its structures. One delegate stated that ‘no one needs to be 
        segregated by USI’ while another argued that candidates for public office should be elected on 
        merit and women did not need to be encouraged to seek nominations.
        
        Speaking to this reporter, SU Welfare officer Aisling Ní Chonaire labeled the decisions 
        ‘incredibly disappointing’ and ‘regressive’. She went on to comment that it was ‘important 
        to realise that these motions were concerned with the ‘fundamental societal and structural 
        barriers, as found in evidence-based research such as ‘Women’s Participation in Politics 
        daily basis. This is seen clearly in our own students’ union, with 60 of our total population 
        comprising of women, but women remain grossly underrepresented in the corridors of influence and power.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_article">Article</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_message">DisplayMessageActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_overview">Overview</string>

</resources>